http://www.isaschools.org/index.php/privacy-policy

About UsOrganizationServicesInternationalismEducation for PeaceEducation for SustainabilityISA Oral English ExamNetworkMember SchoolsMember CompaniesInstitutional PartnersEventsYouth Leadership EncounterISA Annual ConferenceShort Film Competition 2020-2021NewsJoin UsContact
Privacy Policy
The International Schools Assocation (later ISA) is committed to respecting your privacy. We recognise your need for reasonable control of personally identifiable information that you might share with ISA. Personally identifiable information is any information that is associated with your name, your address, telephone and facsimile numbers, e-mail address and any other information about yourself or your company you might furnish to ISA through the use of this website. ISA will use your personally identifiable information for the sole purpose of doing business with you, better understand your needs and, in a general perspective, provide you with better service.
To help us improve your experience, ISA may track your use of this website by mean of “cookies”. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard drive by the ISA web server that will enable ISA to recognise your computer in order to provide you better service and access to this site. A simple manipulation of your browser will allow you to either prevent your browser from accepting cookies, or have your browser notify you if you receive a cookie, or disable cookies altogether. However, disactivation of cookies may impair your viewing of this website so that in order to take full advantage of it, we recommend that you leave them on.
ISA will not sell, rent or otherwise allow third parties to use your personally identifiable information without your consent, understanding that ISA may provide such information to its affiliates for the purpose stated above. ISA affiliates world-wide are bound by this on-line privacy statement.
You may request at any time ISA to update your personally identifiable information or cancel it forthwith from its databases. However, ISA may keep a copy of the cancelled information for legal purposes. Please note that if you do e-commerce with ISA, cancellation will prevent ISA to continue such relationship with you.
NO CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION MUST BE PROVIDED TO ISA THROUGH ANY OF ITS WEBSITES. INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE ISA WEBSITE SHALL BE CONSIDERED AS NON CONFIDENTIAL AND MAY BE USED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT WITHOUT FURTHER RESTRICTIONS
Email
Hits: 21509
Education is the best instrument to build a better world. Living in peace is achieved by working together and celebrating our cultural diversity and similarity.
